ウォルピスカーター  - Blooming in the Mud 泥中に咲く (English lyrics)
Unable to filter the pieces of our broken hearts,
our tears gently dried up,
unable to shed another drop.
“That's funny, isn't it?” we laugh...
A difficult life, maze-like brambles that obstruct you.
The darkness of this corrupt world blocks your path.
You’re someone who’s more depressed than anyone else.
So, right now, we’re probably on the verge of drowning
saved by breathing correctly
now, we simply live for the sake of dying someday.
When we realise why we dislike rain
deep down, we remember
that large soap bubbles
must be really soft and fluffy.
While looking at every colors on the ground
we make sure to walk where there are no puddles.
Surely, you too, would resort to self-defence
if you could avoid a difficult path.
Right now, I am human; today, tomorrow too, and the day after that
it's enough to admit it,
everyone takes in different breaths.
But you too are human,
you just hate being one, that's all.
But you can't hate it, because you're a kind person, you're that someone who would pray for just about anyone.
It takes, for a single blossom to scatter,
water, earth, sunlight and its own seed
Whatever lies right in front of me,
its meaning, past and future,
if a single one of those were missing, nothing would be born: not me, not you, and neither that person.
“It’s nothing” - I say as I burden you with my past.
Destiny getting in your way.
is a misunderstanding. You reap what you sow.
But because this situation is unpleasant,
you want to run away, right?
You want to live, right?
If there is a moment when you feel like throwing yourself,
cleave through the darkness of this world, and let us search for the reason you were born.
The beginning at the end, once it begins, it will be your final life,
at the end of an endless journey, there must be a “time” where it’s now or never.
“It’s impossible to drown in the rain”,
even so, it feels like it’s hard to breathe.
“We live for the sake of dying someday”,
if that is so, if that is so,
we'll never break again. Never. Never. Never
Let the unbroken bells of our hearts resound
everything will be covered by dark clouds and smeared with mud.
Let us draw a line inside the maze that obstructs the path of the world now.
This line will be the overlapping map:
the flower that blooms for the sake of illuminating you.