”Goodbye” and ”Thank you” at the top of my voice
What's more important than grief
Hoping that they reach you as we part
In time for the warmth and pain
I thought it would always be like this
I envisioned our days to come
Why, when our lights calling out to each other
Still burn deep in our hearts?
We met amidst a blazing journey
Coming together, then letting go for the sake of the future
Every time a dream comes true, I’ll remember you
Wishing to become stronger, I cried
with my resolve as the parting gift
Held captive by nostalgic memories
Wailing at the cruelty of this world
There will be even more as I grow older
I never want to lose anything again
By succumbing to the grief
I might not feel pain anymore
But your words, your wishes
I swore to protect them to the end
With a roar, it's crumbling down
Our one and only, irreplaceable world
The bundle of bursting light that I reached out for and held so close
Shimmered, then disappeared for the sake of the future
Going beyond the happiness and promises I've been entrusted
I’ll keep moving forward without glancing behind
Looking straight ahead, I’m going to cry out
Lighting the flames in my heart
Until I reach that distant future…