I don't like you because you're cool
You're cool because I like you
It doesn't matter if others make fun of you
You're my hero, after all
Like how you say you're sleepy
Yet you're always awake for class
You act cool in front of others
But are a big mush in front of dogs
Ah, you're the one I really love
Please be a hero just for me
I want to message you on LINE
I want to walk home together
As you go off to your after-school club
"See you later," I say to myself
I want to see you on weekends
And fall asleep on the phone with you
But I don't have the courage
I really hate this
I want you to turn around and see me
I want you to think of me
I put on perfume
And choke on the scent
I want you so much
And I want to be yours
"Tomorrow will be the day," I say
Fantasizing on my bed
While thinking of you
See you tomorrow
I don't like you because you're cute
You're cute because I like you
It doesn't matter if others make fun of you
You're my heroine, after all
Like how you say you'll stay awake today
Yet always fall asleep in class
How you act like a tomboy in front of everyone
Yet cry surprisingly easily
Ah, you're the one I really love
Won't you be a heroine just for me?
I want to help you with your studies
I want to go see movies together
As you're laughing with friends after class
I say,  "Bye" to myself
I want to be in your story
I want to brag saying, "She's my girlfriend"
But I don't think I can confess
I really hate this
I want you to turn around and see me
I want you to think of me
I put wax in my hair
And get all sticky
I want you so much
And I want to be yours
"Tomorrow will be the day," I say
Fantasizing in my futon
While thinking of you
See you tomorrow
I asked you for advice about you
You asked me for advice about a boy
Don't tell me to give up
Don't go to another boy
Always keep your eyes on me
I want you to turn around and see me
I want you to think of me
Won't you stay by my side forever?
I really love you
I absolutely adore you
"Tomorrow will be the day," I say
I'm fantasizing again today
My love for you
Smelled of sweet musk