​​
Say it​
『Say It.』
Yorushika​
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: n-buna​
Vocal: suis​
Music Video Directed by Ootori​
You see,​
I’ve actually realized already​
Look, about that thing you said​
I didn’t feel like​
thinking about it too much​
So I had forgotten about it, but​
Living blindly, recklessly, delusionally​
Impulsively, impatiently, negatively didn’t do me any good​
I’m sure​
that on the last day of my life,
when I think of what’s gone before​
All of it, all of it will be unspeakably precious, but​
Ah,​
on that last day of my life, you won’t be there–​
More, more, more​
Say that more clearly​
You see,​
I’m not sure how to tell you​
that the sky is blue​
Or what​
I'd have to do to make you understand​
that the clouds at night are high​
Say it​
You see,​
I actually know​
that you're already gone​
You see,​
you’ll probably just call me obstinate,​
and I want to forget, but​
Say it more clearly​
Make a note so you don't forget it​
Let’s meet tomorrow at ten on the train
platform, or something like that​
Even if its petals scatter, a peony is still a flower​
Even if the summer ends,
the memories of it are still cherished​
Put it into words, give voice to it​
Say it​
And then if I could see you on the last day of my life​
I’m sure​
even on the last day of my life, that I’d sing of love​
Because you’d tell me none of it, none of it was in vain​
Ah,​
I still can't believe that on the last day of my life,​
you won't be here​
More, more, more, more​
More, more, more, you have to​
Please,​
say it​
more clearly.​
Translation by EJ/bluepenguin​