Pretender / Official Hige-dandism
( from the movie “THE CONFIDENCEMAN JP” )
[  Covered by KOBASOLO & Harutya  ]
Kimi to no RABU SUTOORII
( You and me, our love story )
Sore wa yosou doori
( It’s just as I imagined )
Iza hajimareba hitori-shibai da
( After the curtain rises, a one-man show starts )
Zutto soba ni itatte
( Though I’m always by your side − )
Kekkyoku tada no kankyaku da
( after all, I’m nothing but the audience )
Kanjou no nai AIMU SOORII
( Said feelingless “I’m sorry” )
Sore wa itsumo doori
( It’s just on a daily basis )
Narete shimaeba waruku wa nai kedo
( That’s not too bad once you get used to it )
Kimi to no ROMANSU wa jinsei-gara
( But I knew my romance with you was unlike myself − )
Tsuzuki wa shinai koto wo shitta
( and I realized it would never last long )
Motto chigau settei de
( In a way different settings − )
Motto chigau kankei de
( in a way different relation )
Deaeru sekaisen erabetara yokatta
( A world line where we can meet − )
( I wish I could choose the way to go )
Motto chigau seikaku de
( In a way different personality − )
Motto chigau kachikan de
( in a way different values − )
Ai wo tsutaeraretara ii na
( I want to send my pure love only to you )
Sou negattemo muda dakara
( ‘Cause I know that wish would’ve been no use − )
GUBBAI
( Goodbye )
Kimi no unmei no hito wa boku ja nai
( I am not the one, the love of your entire life )
Tsurai kedo inamenai
( It’s hard to say, but I can’t deny )
Demo hanaregatai no sa
( Still, I can’t decide to leave )
Sono kami ni fureta dake de
( Just touching your hair, that little thing makes me − )
Itai ya, iya demo
( feel painful-pain, yet − )
Amai na, iya iya
( sweetie-sweet, I can’t say − )
GUBBAI
( Goodbye )
Sore ja boku ni totte kimi wa nani
( What are “you” to me?  I ask myself )
Kotae wa wakaranai
( I don’t have any answers − )
Wakaritaku mo nai no sa
( yes, I don’t want to understand )
Tatta hitotsu
( The only one thing − )
Tashika na koto ga aru to suru no naraba
( if there’s one thing I can say from the bottom of my heart − )
“Kimi wa kirei da”
( “You are beautiful” )
Dareka ga erasou ni kataru ren’ai no ronri
( Hearing someone proudly presents “love and logic” )
Nanihitotsu toshite pin to konakute
( I can’t understand it whatsoever )
Hikouki no mado kara mioroshita
( Just like looking down from the window of a plane − )
Shiranai machi no yakei mitai da
( seeing the night view of a town I don’t know )
Motto chigau settei de
( In a way different settings − )
Motto chigau kankei de
( in a way different relation )
Deaeru sekaisen erabetara yokatta
( A world line where we can meet − )
( I wish I could choose the way to go )
Itatte jun na kokoro de
( From the bottom of a pure heart − )
Kanatta koi wo dakishimete
( holding fulfilled love tight − )
Suki da toka musekinin ni ietara ii na
( I wanted to say “I love you” in a irresponsible way )
Sou negattemo munashii no sa
( But I know that wish would just end in vain )
GUBBAI
( Goodbye )
Tsunaida te no mukou ni ENDO-RAIN
( Holding your hand, distant from the “end line” )
Hikinobasu tabi ni
( Every time I put it off − )
Uzukidasu mirai ni wa
( I see the future starts to ache )
Kimi wa inai, sono jijitsu ni KURAI...
( You’re not by my side )
( Facing that truth makes me cry... )
Sorya kurushii yo na
( It really hurts, doesn’t it? )
GUBBAI
( Goodbye )
Kimi no unmei no hito wa boku ja nai
( I am not the one, the love of your entire life )
Tsurai kedo inamenai
( It’s hard to say, but I can’t deny )
Demo hanaregatai no sa
( Still, I can’t decide to leave )
Sono kami ni fureta dake de
( Just touching your hair, that little thing makes me − )
Itai ya, iya demo
( feel painful-pain, yet − )
Amai na, iya iya
( sweetie-sweet... no, I’ll say − )
GUBBAI
( Goodbye )
Sore ja boku ni totte kimi wa nani
( What are “you” to me?  I ask myself )
Kotae wa wakaranai
( I don’t have any answers − )
Wakaritaku mo nai no sa
( yes, I don’t want to understand )
Tatta hitotsu
( The only one thing − )
Tashika na koto ga aru to suru no naraba
( if there’s one thing I can say from the bottom of my heart − )
“Kimi wa kirei da”
( “You are beautiful” )
Sore mo kore mo ROMANSU no sadame nara
( If all those and these things are the destiny of romance − )
Waruku nai yo na
( not bad, isn’t it? )
Eien mo yakusoku mo nai keredo
( No eternity, no promise, even so − )
“Totemo kirei da”
( “really beautiful” )
[  English Translyrics:  Nate River  ]
2nd Covers Album “これくしょん (Collection) 2”
AVAILABLE NOW on Japanese CD Stores
and/or iTunes, Google Play Music, etc!!
2nd Original Album “Clumsy”
AVAILABLE NOW:  comes with 8 songs
on iTunes, Google Play Music, etc!!