Hated by Life Itself
"Inochi ni Kirawareteiru"
命に嫌われている。
Song and Lyrics by Kanzaki Iori
Covered by:
Kobasolo (コバソロ) & Aizawa (相沢)
"shinitai nante iu na yo.
"Don't say you want to die."
akiramenai de ikiro yo."
"Live on without giving up!"
sonna uta ga tadashii nante, bakageteru yo na.
It is ridiculous to say that songs
with that kind of lyrics are correct
jissai jibun wa shinde mo yokute
To be honest, I wouldn't care at all if I died,
mawari ga shindara kanashikute
But I'd be pretty sad if the people around me did,
"sore ga iya dakara" tte iu, ego nan desu.
I suppose it's some kind of ego, that goes:
"Because I just wouldn't like it."
tanin ga ikite mo dou demo yokute
Having no care whatsoever whether
strangers live or not,
dareka o kirau koto mo fasshon de
And hating someone else just seems like
some kind of fashion now,
soredemo "heiwa ni ikiyou" nante
But “Live peacefully” nevertheless?
suteki na koto deshou.
What a wonderful thing that would be indeed...
gamen no saki de wa dareka ga shinde
On the other side of the screen, someone dies,
sore o nageite dareka ga utatte
Lamenting that someone else sings,
sore ni kanka sareta shounen ga
Influenced by that, a young boy
naifu o motte hashitta.
Ran off carrying a knife
bokura wa inochi ni kirawarete iru.
We are hated by life itself.
kachikan mo ego mo oshitsukete
Forcing values and ego,
itsumo dareka o koroshitai uta o
We so very simply broadcast songs about
kantan ni denpa de nagashita.
Wanting to kill somebody over radio waves
bokura wa inochi ni kirawarete iru.
We are hated by life itself.
karugarushiku shinitai datoka
We who thoughtlessly say we want to die
karugarushiku inochi o miteru
And look at life carelessly,
bokura wa inochi ni kirawarete iru.
Are hated by it.
okane ga nai node kyou mo, ichinichijuu damin o ouka suru
Since I’ve got no money, again,
I enjoy sleeps of idleness throughout the day
ikiru imi nante midasezu, muda o jikaku shite iki o suru.
Still without grasping the meaning of life, I come to an epiphany that it’s pointless and so I take a breath.
sabishii nante kotoba de kono kizu ga arawasete ii mono ka
Is is really OK to express this wound with the words,
“I’m lonely”?
sonna iji bakari kakae kyou mo hitori beddo ni nemuru
Carrying nothing else but such obstinacy,
today I sleep alone on my bed again
shounen datta bokutachi wa
We who were but youths
itsuka seinen ni kawatteku.
At some point start to change into young adults.
toshioite itsuka kareha no you ni
Growing old, one day we rot away like fallen leaves,
dare ni mo shirarezu kuchite iku.
Without a single soul in the world knowing of about it
fujimi no karada o te ni irete,
Obtaining an immortal body,
isshou shinazu ni ikite iku.
and living our whole lives without dying…
sonna SF o mousou shiteru
...I’m just daydreaming about
these kinds of science fiction situations.
jibun ga shinde mo dou demo yokute
I couldn’t care a bit if I died,
soredemo mawari ni ikite hoshikute
But still, I want others to live.
mujun o kakaete ikiteku nante
Living on with these contradictions...
okorarete shimau.
I think I’ll get yelled at.
"tadashii mono wa tadashiku inasai."
“Things that are 'correct' should stay 'correct'."
"shinitakunai nara ikite inasai."
“If you don’t want to die, then live.”
kanashiku naru nara soredemo ii nara
If you’re going to end up sad and if that’s fine,
zutto hitori de warae yo.
Then you gotta laugh alone forever.
bokura wa inochi ni kirawarete iru.
We are hated by life itself.
koufuku no imi sura wakarazu,
Without even grasping the meaning of joy,
umareta kankyou bakari nikunde
We just hate the hand life has dealt us,
kantan ni kako bakari noro u.
And merely curse our pasts
bokura wa inochi ni kirawarete iru.
We are hated by life itself.
sayonara bakari ga sukisugite
We who simply like the idea
of “goodbyes” a little too much,
hontou no wakare nado shiranai
And not truly know about what a "true farewell" is,
bokura wa inochi ni kirawarete iru
Are hated by life itself.
koufuku mo
Happiness,
wakare mo
Farewells,
aijou mo
Love,
yuujou mo
And friendship;
kokkei na yume no tawamure de
They’re all illusions of comical dreams
zenbu kane de kaeru shiromono.
That can be bought for money…
ashita shinde shimau kamo shirenai.
I might just die tomorrow you know,
subete muda ni naru kamo shirenai.
Everything might just end up being for naught.
asa mo
At mornings
yoru mo
And nights,
haru mo
On Spring
aki mo
And Autumn,
kawarazu dareka ga doko ka de shinu.
Unchanging, someone dies somewhere
yume mo asu mo nani mo iranai
I don’t need dreams or even a tomorrow,
kimi ga ikite ita nara sore de ii
If you’ll have lived on then that’s all I need
sou da
Yeah...
hontou wa
That’s actually...
sou iu koto ga utaitai.
What I want to sing about
inochi ni kirawarete iru
Hated by life itself.
kekkyoku itsuka wa shinde iku.
In the end, we will all die eventually
kimi datte
You will,
boku datte
I will,
itsuka wa kareha no you ni kuchiteku
One day, all of us will rot away like fallen leaves.
soredemo bokura wa hisshi ni ikite
But regardless, we live on desperately–
inochi o hisshi ni kakaete ikite
Holding onto our lives, desperately, we live–
koroshite
Killing,
agaite
Struggling,
waratte
Laughing,
kakaete
Embracing it all,
ikite
Living,
Living, Living,
ikite
Living, Living, Living,
Living, Living, Living, Living–
ikiro~
Just live~.
"Inochi ni Kirawareteiru"
(Hated by Life Itself)
命に嫌われている。
Song and Lyrics by Kanzaki Iori
Covered by: Kobasolo (コバソロ) & Aizawa (相沢)