YOUR LIE IN APRIL
The spring with you seems like it hasn't started yet,
and the blowing wind softly caresses the falling petals
You've stepped towards me just like how you used to
run away with me on the green field
The song's melody with the evening sunlight gently brought us together forever
Faintly whispered all the honest things we had kept in our hearts
All these long roads made us exhausted, and we once fell
April you were here looking at me smiling
The petals wither too quickly, you had flown away, you had gone far away
April is sometimes too fragile for us to say all the words in our heart
If only I had trusted you for once,
the girl I loved now has gone with the winds
Leaving April there...
The spring without you seems to have started
And the blowing wind unwittingly sweeps away the falling petals
You hastily hid away under the evening sun rays
Leaving only footprints on the vast green field
The quiet melody in the middle of a late afternoon brought us closer forever
Faintly whispered all the honest things we had kept in our hearts
All these long roads make me exhausted, I have fallen once
April starlight suddenly fades away in the distant
The petals wither too quickly, you had flown away, you had gone away
April is sometimes too fragile for us to say all the words in our heart
If only I had trusted you for once,
the girl I loved now has gone with the winds
Leaving April there...
And I will live like what you used to dream of
And I will step forward on the road I'd chosen
And when I die will smile to see you
Gently greet my April girl...
All the memories fade too quickly, you had flown away, you had gone far away
April is sometimes too fragile for us to say...
If only I had trusted you for once,
the girl I loved now has gone with the winds
Leaving April forever...
Leaving April to myself...