Boku wa ima mukuchi na sora ni
( I’m standing here, looking up the silent sky )
Hakidashita kodoku to iu na no kumo
( I’m letting out all the clouds − or “loneliness”, I would say )
Sono kumo ga ame wo furasete
( Thanks to those, all the clouds cause rain to fall )
Niji ga deru, douse tsukamenai noni
( A rainbow appears − I know, I can’t catch it at all )
Hajimete no KISU wo
( I still remember how we kissed − )
Kurikaeshite hoshikute
( wanted one more time, for the first time )
Ai ga boku ni kamitsuite hanasanai to iu keredo
( “Love bites me, it never goes away” )
( I can’t believe whatever you say )
Samishisa no katachi wa kawaranai mitai da
( The pain never goes away )
( Is it the shape of loneliness? )
Maiagatte yuke, itsuka yoru no mukougawa
( Fly high above the sky − )
( far away, beyond the night )
Unzari suru hodo hikare, kimi no uta
( Even if you’re tired of it − )
( burn up my heart − this is your song )
Yasashisa ga nigotta hibi no
( “Be considerate” − but I feel it’s got a cloud )
Yuutsu wa man’in-densha mitai da
( “Melancholy” − I just feel it’s like a crowded train )
Sameta nukumori wo
( I still remember how you’re warm − )
Muyami ni hoorinageta
( can’t tell, but I just threw it in a rush )
Boku ga ai wo shinjite mo kitto inakunarun darou
( Even if I could believe in your love − )
( you would leave anyway, I’m sure )
Sore nara iranai, kanashisugiru kara
( Then I would say “I don’t need you” − )
( ‘cause sorrow filled my heart enough )
Sayounara sae mo umaku ienasou dakara
( I don’t think I can tell any − )
( even a little thing, even “goodbye” )
Te wo furu kawari ni dakishimete mita yo
( Instead of just waving hands − )
( holding you tight was all I could do )
Nagareboshi wo mita
( I saw a little shooting star )
Negau boku no uta
( This is my song wishing for you )
Soba ni iru dakede
( It was just staying by your side )
Honto shiawase datta na
( Yes, it’s just how much I need )
Soba ni iru dakede, tada soredake de sa
( Just staying by your side − it was the only thing I need )
Ai ga boku ni kamitsuite hanasanai to iu keredo
( “Love bites me, it never goes away” )
( I can’t believe whatever you say )
Samishisa no katachi wa kawaranai mitai da
( The pain never goes away )
( Is it the shape of loneliness? )
Maiagatte yuke, itsuka yoru no mukougawa
( Fly high above the sky − )
( far away, beyond the night )
Unzari suru hodo hikare, kimi no uta
( Even if you’re tired of it − )
( burn up my heart − this is your song )
Mou kizutsukanai, mou kizutsukenai
( Yes, I won’t be hurt anymore − )
( I swear, I won’t hurt anymore )
Hikare, kimi no uta
( This is your song − burn up my heart! )
1st Full Album “KOBASOLO”
AVAILABLE NOW on Kobasolo Online Store
and/or iTunes, Amazon Music, etc!!
Covers Album “これくしょん (Collection)”
AVAILABLE NOW on Japanese CD Stores
and/or iTunes, Amazon Music, etc!!